Penghui Zhang | Curriculum Vitae

699 South Mill Ave - Tempe, Arizona, USA - 85281

☑ Penghui.Zhang@asu.edu • ⑤ formerbuckeye.github.io/me/

Education

Ph.D., Computer Engineering

Aug 2016-Present

Ariona State University, Tempe, AZ

Advisor: Adam Doupé & Gail-Joon Ahn

M.S., Electrical and Computer Engineering

Aug 2014-May 2016

The Ohio State University, Columbus, OH

Advisor: Xiaorui (Ray) Wang

Thesis: Temperature Balancing among Servers with Workload Distribution

B.E., Information Engineering

Aug 2010-Jul 2014

Beijing Institute of Technology, Beijing, China

Publications

Conference Papers with Proceedings (refereed).....

- o Zhibo Sun, Adam Oest, **Penghui Zhang**, Carlos Rubio-Medrano, Tiffany Bao, Ruoyu Wang, Ziming Zhao, Yan Shoshitaishvili, Adam Doupe, and Gail-Joon Ahn, "Having Your Cake and Eating It: An Analysis of Concession-Abuse-as-a-Service," *to appear in the Proceedings of the 30th USENIX Security Symposium*, Aug 2021, Vancouver, B.C., CANADA.
- Penghui Zhang, Adam Oest, Haehyun Cho, Zhibo Sun, RC Johnson, Brad Wardman, Shaown Sarker, Alexandros Kapravelos, Tiffany Bao, Ruoyu Wang, Yan Shoshitaishvili, Adam Doupé, and Gail-Joon Ahn, "CrawlPhish: Large-scale Analysis of Client-side Cloaking Techniques in Phishing," to appear in the Proceedings of the 42nd IEEE Symposium on Security & Privacy, May 2021, San Francisco, CA.
- o Marzieh Bitaab, Haehyun Cho, Adam Oest, **Penghui Zhang**, Zhibo Sun, Rana Pourmohamad, Doowon Kim, Tiffany Bao, Ruoyu Wang, Yan Shoshitaishvili, Adam Doupe, and Gail-Joon Ahn, "Scam Pandemic: How Attackers Exploit Public Fear through Phishing," to appear in the Proceedings of the 2020 APWG Symposium on Electronic Crime Research (eCrime).
- Adam Oest, Yeganeh Safaei, Penghui Zhang, Brad Wardman, Kevin Tyers, Yan Shoshitaishvili, Adam Doupé, and Gail-Joon Ahn, "PhishTime: Continuous Longitudinal Measurement of the Effectiveness of Anti-phishing Blacklists," in the Proceedings of the 29th USENIX Security Symposium(USENIX), Aug 2020, Boston, MA.
- Adam Oest, Penghui Zhang, Brad Wardman, Eric Nunes, Jakub Burgis, Ali Zand, Kurt Thomas, Adam Doupé, and Gail-Joon Ahn, "Sunrise to Sunset: Analyzing the End-to-end Life Cycle and Effectiveness of Phishing Attacks at Scale," in the Proceedings of the 29th USENIX Security Symposium(USENIX), Aug 2020, Boston, MA.

- Penghui Zhang, Haehyun Cho, Ziming Zhao, Adam Doupé, and Gail-Joon Ahn, "iCORE: Continuous and Proactive Extrospection on Multi-core IoT Devices," in Proceedings of the 34th ACM/SIGAPP Symposium On Applied Computing (SAC), Limassol, Cyprus, Apr 2019. (24% acceptance rate.)
- o Haehyun Cho, **Penghui Zhang**, Donguk Kim, Jinbum Park, Choong-Hoon Lee, Ziming Zhao, Adam Doupé, and Gail-Joon Ahn, "Prime+Count: Novel Cross-world Covert Channels on ARM TrustZone," in Proceedings of the 34th Annual Computer Security Applications Conference (ACSAC), San Juan, Puerto Rico, USA, Dec 2018. (20% acceptance rate.)

Service

Technical Program Committee.....

- o 42nd IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy (IEEE S&P, Shadow Committee)
- 2021 International Conference on Secure Knowledge Management in the Artificial Intelligence Era (SKM)
- 2020 The Fourteenth International Conference on Advanced Engineering Computing and Applications in Sciences (ADVCOMP)

Session Chair.....

2019 IoT Session on ACM/SIGAPP Symposium On Applied Computing (SAC)

Journal Reviewer.....

- Computers & Security
- o Journal of Information Processing Systems

External Reviewer

o 2020 ACM Conference on Data and Application Security and Privacy (CODASPY)

Experience Summary

Graduate Research AssistantSEFCOM - Security Engineering for Future Computing

InfoSec Intern PhD

Applied Research Team
Technical Intern PhD

CFIA - Cyber-Fraud Intel.& Analytics

Graduate Teaching Assistant CSE 230, CSE 110, CSE 469

Software Developer
Radar Lab

Arizona State University

May 2020–Aug 2020

PayPal Inc.

May 2019–Aug 2019

Jan 2017-Present

PayPal Inc.

Aug 2016–May 2017

Arizona State University

May 2013–Jul 2014

Beijing Institute of Tech.

Technical Strengths

• **Programming Languages:** C, Java, Assembly, Python, Matlab, JavaScript, TeX Also basic ability with: C++, PHP, VHDL.

o Skills: System and Script Programming, JavaScript Cloaking Analysis

o Operating Systems: Linux, OP-TEE OS, Windows

Computer Architectures: ARM

Honors and Awards

Distinguished Paper Award

Second Place Facebook's Internet Defense Prize

"Sunrise to Sunset: Analyzing the End-to-end Life Cycle and Effectiveness of Phishing Attacks at Scale," by the Organizing Committee of the 29th USENIX Security Symposium and Facebook.

Engineering Graduate Fellowship

from Ira A. Fulton Schools of Engineering, Arizona State University, 2020

o Ferdinand A. Stanchi Fellowship

from Arizona State University, 2019

Distinguished Poster Award

"SeCore: Continuous Extrospection with High Visibility on Multi-core ARM Platforms," by the Organizing Committee of the 8th ACM Conference on Data and Application Security and Privacy (CODASPY '18).

Academic Excellence Scholarship

from Beijing Institute of Technology, Beijing, China

References

o Gail-Joon Ahn: Email: gahn@asu.edu

Professor

Fulton Entrepreneurial Professor

Director, Center for Cybersecurity and Digital Forensics

Director, Laboratory of Security Engineering for Future Computing (SEFCOM)

School of Computing, Informatics and Decision Systems Engineering

Ira A. Fulton Schools of Engineering

Arizona State University

o Adam Doupé:

Associate Professor

Co-Director, Center for Cybersecurity and Digital Forensics

co-Director, Laboratory of Security Engineering for Future Computing (SEFCOM)

School of Computing, Informatics and Decision Systems Engineering

Ira A. Fulton Schools of Engineering

Arizona State University

Email: doupe@asu.edu